CHIRANJEEVI G

chiranjeevi.naidu1312@gmail.com +91 8073761695 Bangalore, India morpheuslord@protonmail.com github.com/morpheuslord **13/12/2002**

Personal Blogs TryHackMe

Profile Webpage

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

As a passionate cybersecurity enthusiast with a keen eye for critical analysis, I bring a robust skill set in system, network, and web hacking. My dedication to continuous learning keeps me at the forefront of the latest security trends and technologies. My proficiency extends to articulate article writing, where I have contributed numerous pieces on security topics, aiding others in understanding complex concepts. I approach every task as an opportunity to grow and excel, eagerly embracing challenges as avenues for further skill enhancement and professional development. My career in cybersecurity has been characterized by a neverending quest for excellence and knowledge. I'm constantly excited to learn more about the technical facets of security and improve my abilities in risk assessment, threat analysis, and strategic security planning, among other areas.

SKILLS

Hard Skills:

· Programming: Python Automation Programming, Red Team tool development.

in /in/chiranjeevi-q-naidu

- Red Teaming: Web application testing, System Exploitation testing.
- · Network VAPT: Network Enumeration, Exploitation, Vulnerability Analysis.
- AWS: Terraform, Docker, Docker-Compose, G.O.A.T Development, IAC, Security Automation.
- · Writing: Writing Technical Paper, Blog content (100000+ Reads on personal blogs).
- · AI: Worked with AI models such as OpenAI GPT3, and Meta LLama.
- · Tools: Sbom-tool, Trivy, Syft, Latex.

Soft Skills:

Communication, Teamwork, Project Management, Adaptability, Problem Solving

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Applications - Jain (Deemed-To-Be-University) 3/2021 - 3/2024

Undergraduate

Scored Average GPA - 8.455

PUC(SEBA) - Presidency University 3/2018 - 3/2021

Scored 87.6%

4/2019 SSLC - Sri Chaitanya Techno School

Scored 75%

School

PUC

WORK EXPERIENCE

7/2023 - 3/2024 Offensive Security Engineer **Avercyber Technologies**

Worked on IAS, and AWS infrastructure security, Involved in building G.O.A.T Projects and related deploy-

Cybersecurity Engineer

Avercyber Technologies

Worked on Offensive tools development and product improvement research.

5/2023 - 7/2023

1/2023 - 12/2023 Freelance Developer and Content Writer

Developed tools and wrote contents for a few clients.

PROJECTS

Nmap API Github Link

- Python
- · AI (Llama and GPT3)
- A Nmap API was developed with a focus on deployment speed and ease.
- · Flask Framework
- · The project is always evolving, demonstrating a dedication to frequent updates and enhancements.

GPT_Vuln-analyzer Github Link

- Pvthon
- AI (Llama and GPT3)
- Vulnerability Analysis
- A Proof of Concept application was developed to demonstrate the usefulness of AI in precise vulnerability analysis.
- Enabled extensive cybersecurity features in a single, integrated tool, such as DNS reconnaissance and subdomain enumeration.

QuadraInspect Github Link

- Python
- Reverse Engineering
- Android Testing
- Developed QuadraInspect, an Android security analysis framework that integrates tools for comprehensive app vulnerability detection and security assessment, with features for downloading and updating tools to enhance framework capabilities.

HackBot Github Link

- Python
- AI (Llama and GPT3)
- Developed HackBot, an AI-driven cybersecurity chatbot designed to provide accurate responses to cybersecurity-related questions.
- Developed with security researchers and ethical hackers in mind, it can conduct code analysis as well as scan analysis.

Brute-Hacking-Framework

Github Link

- Python
- Custom
 Framework
- Developed an all-in-one system framework for all the possible tools that are compatible with Windows which has maximum portability.

CVE-LLM_Dataset Github Link

AI (Llama and GPT)

• Developed a dataset as a proof of concept for research involving AI training and the complexities related to cybersecurity implementations.

PUBLICATIONS

Cybersecurity

AI-BASED ENUMERATION AND EXPLOIT SUGGESTER

JETI

This research is intended to implement Artificial Intelligence with Cyber Security. Our main goal of this research is to make an AI that can gather information and search for the best possible exploits and all the vulnerabilities.

Cybersecurity

API Based Network Scanning

MAPAN

This paper is written on improving the stability and overall usability of a system involving network vulnerability scanning. This paper involves a resource managing utility over a virtual client to achieve this goal.

HONORS AND CERTIFICATIONS

Competition Certificate of Merit

BGS

Won first place in a research presentation competition hosted by BGS College of Engineering and Technology.

Honor Certificate of Appreciation

JAIN

Awarded by Jain(Deemed To Be University) for being the speaker in the IRDCSTEM-2023 post-conference learning.

LANGUAGES

English, Tamil, Kannada, Telugu

DECLARATION

I solemnly declare that the information in this resume is true to the best of my knowledge and belief. All information in this resume is right and truthful. I just wanted to let you know that the information and details shared in this resume are correct and inclusive. I take full liability for the correctness of the information.